

# Shuo-Wen Hsu

Hi, I'm a 2nd-year master student working on novel HCI research in Interaction Design and Development Lab at National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan led by Prof. Da-Yuan Huang. Before that, I received my bachelor's degree in Industrial Design. Our previous works include MASQUE - a skin-stretching Head-Mounted Display generates haptic feedback on human face, GAITERS - a skin-stretching device generates haptic feedback on lower limbs, and GLISSADE - a weight-shifting digital pen to facilitate input. These works have been or will be presented at top-tier conferences, including CHI and UIST.



Taipei, Taiwan



shuowenh@gmail.com



https://issuu.com/shuo-wenhsu/docs/portfolio

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Scenario Lab

UX Design intern 06/2018 - 09/2018

Macauto Group - Innovative Products for **Automotive Interiors** Design engineer 09/2016 - 02/2018

#### **AGUA** Design

Design intern 07/2015 - 09/2015

#### CONFERENCE TALK

# [UIST'19] Conference Proceeding Talk

October 20-23,2019 New Orleans, LA, USA

# **LANGUAGES**

Mandarin Native language English Fluent (TOEFL 101) French Intermediate

# **SKILLS**















# **EDUCATION**

### National Chiao Tung University, Hsinchu, Taiwan

Master of Art in Industrial design, Institute of Applied Arts 2018 - 2019 Advisor: Dr. Da-Yuan Huang

National Yunlin University of Science and Technology, Yunlin, Taiwan Bachelor of Design in Industrial Design 2012 - 2016

Groupe École Supérieure de Commerce de Troyes, Troyes, France Exchange Student, Champagne School of Design 2014 - 2015

# **PUBLICATIONS**

[CHI 2020 Paper] Chi Wang, Da-Yuan Huang, Shuo-wen Hsu, Cheng-Lung Lin, Yeu-Luen Chiu, Chu-En Hou, Bing-Yu Chen Gaiters: Exploring Skin Stretch Feedback on Legs for Enhancing Virtual Reality Experiences

[CHI 2020 Paper] Kai-Chieh Huang, Da-Yuan Huang, Chen-Kuo Sun, Ruei-Che Chang, Shuo-wen Hsu, Chih-Yun Yang, Bing-Yu Chen Glissade: Generating Balance Shifting Feedback to Facilitate **Auxiliary Digital Pen Input** 



🕎 Best Paper Honorable Mention Award

[UIST 2019 Paper] Chi Wang, Da-Yuan Huang, Shuo-wen Hsu, Chu-En Hou, Yeu-Luen Chiu, Ruei-Che Chang, Jo-Yu Lo, Bing-Yu Chen Masque: Exploring Lateral Skin Stretch Feedback on the Face with Head-Mounted Displays

#### **SCHOLARSHIPS & AWARDS**

## **MOST Funding Program of Attending International Conference** for Graduate Students 2019

Ministry of Science and Technology, Taiwan

#### Academic Excellence Award 2019

Institute of Applied Arts, National Chiao Tung University

#### Young Pin Design Award 2016

Manufacturer Sponsorship Award Best Design Award - Nominated

# Scholarships for Excellent Students to Study Abroad 2014 Ministry of Education, Taiwan